## MIRA **IZZATUL**

Malaysia · +60176245741

Email · LinkedIn · GitHub · Portfolio

Dedicated game programmer with over 5 years of experience in developing interactive gameplay system and UI seeking an efficient position in game development with a company that prides itself on their positive company culture, compassionate, and like-minded people.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### **LANGUAGES**

UE Blueprints/C++(5 years), Unity C#(1 Year)

#### **SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE**

Unreal Engine 4 & 5, Visual Studio, Github, Perforce, Tortoise SVN, Unity

#### **EXPERIENCE**

JUL 2022 - PRESENT

### **GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER (REMOTE), DEEP FIELD GAMES**

#### **Abiotic Factor**

- Developed the core foundation of the cooking and pet system, supporting in-world placement/interaction.
- Investigated and implemented Push Model networking into the existing game, migrating existing C++
  replicated code to use the new method.
- Expanded the save system to support an open world style save structure, with a large amount of
  modifiable furniture, resources and individual player saves.
- Extensive work using UMG, working with Designers and Player feedback to implement new functionality across Player HUD and Inventory/Crafting menus.
- Implemented stable fixes across the entire project for live hotfixes.
- Expanded player mechanic to include custom movement eg. Jetpack, combat roll. Improved interaction system to allow player interaction like applying medical items or offering food.
- Implemented melee/projectile combat system for players, including unique weapons eg. Vacuum, net launcher.
- Worked with designers to implement perks and new buffs for players and creatures eg. Skill tree bonuses, altered player mechanics based on skill level.

# JAN 2019 – JUN 2022

## **GAME PROGRAMMER, TODAK STUDIOS SDN BHD**

#### ToGather:Island

- Developed a projectile system for easy tuning for NPCs.
- Rebuilt mouse and keyboard input support for inventory and crafting while preserving controller compatibility.
- Expanded the player progression system for a reliable save/load functionality across sessions.

## **Unannounced title**

- Worked on multiplayer fighting gameplay mechanics and systems.
- Worked on MOBA core gameplay, game mechanic, system and UI.
- Worked on multiplayer twin stick shooter core gameplay, controls, systems and Al.
- Assisted programmers and designers for the best gameplay implementation.
- Assisted team in source control management.

## SEP 2018 - JAN 2019

### **UNITY PROGRAMMER, NILAM PUBLICATION SDN BHD**

Worked on several games and simulations for digital educational purposes.

# MAY 2017 - SEP 2017

## **3D GAME DEVELOPER.** ESOLUTION TECHNOLOGY SERVICES

Lead a team of developer developed an embedded web application using Unity 3D.

# **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2017

### **DEGREE TITLE, UNIVERSITI TEKNIKAL MALAYSIA MELAKA**

Bachelors of Information Technology, Game Technology